嘿  伙计们...
Hey, guys--
等等  我来跟他们讲
Wait! Let me tell them.
-好  -乔伊要...
- Sure. - Joey's gonna be...
在一个益智节目中做嘉宾了
...a celebrity guest on a game show.
真的  哪个节目
Really? Which one?
鱼  海草
Fish. Seaweed.
-沉船…  -海中之物…
- A sunken ship. - Things you find in the ocean.
-你要上《智力金字塔》   -对
- You're gonna be on Pyramid! - Yeah.
哦  那是我们最喜欢的益智节目了
That was our favorite game show ever.
除了《匹配赛》以外
Except for Match Game.
还有《输赢平》
Or Win, Lose or Draw.
瞧瞧我结的亲家
What did I marry into?
你们想明天
You guys wanna come
来看我录节目吗
and watch me tape the show?
不行
Oh, we can't.
我们要给菲比开个婚前告别单身狂欢
We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
对喽  抱歉  兄弟们  此路不通
Yeah. Sorry, boys, this ride's closing.
我和钱德勒要参加一个白痴校友聚会
And Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
难以置信你要跟多尼·奥斯蒙德做节目
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
当真
Seriously?
罗斯和我
Ross and I
以前总想学多尼和马瑞一样
always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
你们俩还越说越起劲儿了
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
对  我们以前还在
Yeah, we used to perform
家里和朋友面前表演过嘞
for our family and friends.
哦  没错  我还真给它忘了
Oh, God, that's right. I blocked that out.
我要离开你了
I'm leaving you.
《老友记》  第十季  第11集  脱衣舞男之泪
Friends S10E11 The One Where The Stripper Cries
又见到这些人
It's so weird to
太奇怪了
see all these people again.
我的天啊  看
Oh, my God, look.
那是杰佛·克拉瑞
There's Jeffrey Klarik.
谁
Who?
约翰·卢瑟夫的室友
He was roommates with John Rosoff.
他当时跟安卓·特布里诺拍拖
He went out with Andrea Tamborino.
她后来又跟迈克尔·斯克劳夫好上了
She dumped him for Michael Skloff.
我上的是这所学校吗
Did I go to this school?
嘿  那是米西·戈尔伯格
Hey, there's Missy Goldberg.
你肯定记得她
You gotta remember her.
当然  她很正点
Sure. Nice.
哥们儿  你可跟我老妹结了婚的
Dude, you're married to my sister.
你说的没错
You're right.
我夸她正点
By saying "nice,"
就是在舔她了
I'm virtually licking her.
嘿  我听说她又单身了
Hey, I hear she's single again.
你说我是不是该跟她约会呢
You think I should ask her out?
你是不是想要
Are you asking permission
打破君子协定
to break the pact?
是的  求你了
Yes, please.
瞧瞧乐队的传单
Hey. Hey, check out the fliers for the band.
我在机房的苹果机上做的
I made them on a Macintosh in the computer room.
超赞的
Awesome.
名字还挺醒目的
The name really stands out.
这多亏有了瑞士粗体24点
Thanks to a little something called Helvetica Bold 24-point.
哥们儿  我们要在"亚学联"盖了
Man, we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
-嘿  伙计们   -嘿  米西
- Hey, guys. - Hey, Missy.
你知道吗  我们乐队星期五演出
Our band is playing on Friday.
是啊  你该来看看
Yeah, you should come check us out.
我们的乐队名叫"行  还是不行"
We're called Way/No Way.
-不行   -行
- No way. - Way.
-好吧  到时见 -新鲜
- Great. I'll be there. - Fresh.
-老板. -薄荷.
- Boss. - Mint.
-她走了   -我知道
- She's gone. - I know it.
你知道吗  我一定要约到她
I am totally gonna ask her out.
哥们儿  我还想约她呢
Dude, I was gonna ask her out.
是我先说的  兄弟
I said it first, bro.
那我还先想到的呢  老哥
Well, I thought it first, Homes.
听着  你要是约…
Look, if you date--
等等  我们在干吗呢
Wait! Wait! What are we doing?
我们俩有太重要的事情
What we have is too important
可不能重色轻友反目成仇
to mess it up over some girl.
再说  天涯何处无芳草
I mean, we can get laid any time we want.
就是
Totally.
我高中就跟人上过床
I had sex in high schoo.
我也是  我是情场高手
Me too. I'm good at it.
好吧  我们俩立个君子协定
All right, I say we make a pact.
谁都不许跟米西·戈尔伯格约会
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
一言为定
You got it.
那么  现在我们就不能跟米西·戈尔伯格
That's Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates
菲比·凯特
and Molly Ringwald...
还有莫莉·里沃特约会了
...who we can't go out with.
就是这么说的
Those are the pacts.
哦  还有西娜·伊斯特
And Sheena Easton.
反正我们也追不上她
But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
或许你追不上吧
Maybe not you.
好吧  我正式授权
Well, I officially give you permission
允许你打破君子协定
to break the pact.
谢谢
Thank you.
好  我要上啦
All right. Here I go.
嘿  还记得上学时
Hey, remember how scary it used to be
跟女孩说话都慌神吗
going up to girls in college?
你的手在发抖呢
Your hands are shaking.
我知道  我还一个劲地冒汗
I know. And I can't stop sweating.
5  4  3  鼓掌
Five, four, three. Applause.
哦
Yeah!
欢迎大家
Welcome.
这里是肥皂剧之周  《智力金字塔》
It is Soap Opera Week here on Pyramid.
来看看选手们
Let's meet our contestants.
首先  是数据库专家金·拉斯特
First, Gene Lester is a database specialist.
他的搭档是
He's gonna be playing with
《我们的日子》剧中的明星
Days of Our Lives star
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
嘿  我知道普通人跟名人
I know it can be intimidating
在一起时都会紧张
for regular people to be around celebrities...
不过没事儿
...but relax.
我跟你差不多
I'm just like you,
就是好看点儿  钱多点儿
only better-looking and richer.
…要跟《综合医院》剧中的
She'll be playing with
明星莱丝莉·查尔森搭档
star of General Hospital, Leslie Charleson.
欢迎大家  祝各位好运
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you.
我们开始玩《智力金字塔》  好吗
Let's play Pyramid.
我们在节目开始之前
All right? Now, we flipped a coin
已经抛过硬币了
before the show.
金  你猜对硬币    你先开始
Gene, you won the toss, so you'll start.
你喜欢什么类型
Which category would you like?
我选择"你越线了"
I will take "You Crossed the Line."
"你越线了"  乔伊
"You Crossed the Line." Joey...
你给金描述那些有线条的东西
...describe for Gene these things that have lines.
限时20秒
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
预备  开始
Ready? Go.
SUPERMARKET:超市
象超市一样的商店...
Okay, it's a store like a supermarket.
NOTEBOOK:笔记本
我知道犯规了
I see what I did there.
好吧  好吧  我写…
Okay, okay. I'm writing in my....
日记
Diary.
不是  差不多接近笔记本
No, more like a notebook.
BLUEPRINT:蓝图
要是我建所房子  设计图
If I'm building a house, the plan...
不是叫什穆图…
...isn't called a "shmooprint" ....
带个"图"字都不行
I can't do that either?
FOOTBALLFIELD:足球场
在高中
In high school,
有一次我跟个女孩做爱
I once had sex with a girl
就在某地中央
right in the middle of the...?
自助餐厅
Cafeteria?
是有过那么一次  但那不是他们要的那个词
Yeah, but they're not looking for that.
真的太感谢你们为此做的一切
Thank you so much for this.
哦  你喜欢吗
You like it?
我的天啊   还挺高雅的呢
Oh, my God, it's all so elegant.
什么时候开始来点儿刺激的
When's the dirty stuff starting?
什么
What?
你知道的
You know.
脱衣舞啦  男子艳舞啦
The strippers and the guys dancing...
小便四处飞散
...and, you know, pee-pees flying about.
菲比  我…
Pheebs, l....
今天没有什么"四处飞散"
There isn't gonna be any "flying about."
事实上  我们觉得我们老大不小的了
We actually thought we were a little too mature
还玩这些
for stuff like that.
哦  好吧
Oh, okay.
我知道你们在干吗  好的
I see what you're doing. That's fine.
今天就是个茶话会  好的
This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
好淫荡啊
Raunchy.
真的  菲比
Seriously, Pheebs,
这不是那种狂欢
it's not gonna be that kind of a party.
真的  这就是
Really? So this is...?
我的婚前单身告别会
This is my big sendoff into married life?
瑞秋  我可就只有这一次单身告别会啊
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever gonna have.
我钱包里装了好多一块的钱呢
I've got a big wad of ones in my purse.
真的  今天就只是茶话会
Really? I mean, really? It's just tea?
当然不是了
No.
菲比  还有别的呢
Phoebe, of course there's more.
好吧
Okay.
我是说  我去问问莫妮卡
I mean, let me just go talk to Monica...
看什么时候上艳舞啊
...and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
现在  金  我要提醒你
Now, Gene, I must remind you,
必须答对6题才能留下来
you need all six of these to stay in the game.
给乔伊描述
Describe for Joey
"冰箱里的物品"
"things you find in your refrigerator."
我看这简直是给我们送分啊
They might as well just give us the points.
限时20秒
Give me 20 seconds on the clock.
预备  开始
Ready? Go.
CREAM:奶油
你往咖啡里加的东西
You put this in your coffee.
勺子  手  脸
A spoon. Your hands. Your face.
它是白色的
It's white.
纸  雪  鬼
Paper. Snow. A ghost!
它比牛奶重
It's heavier than milk.
石头  狗  地球
A rock. A dog. The Earth.
过
Pass.
MAYONNAISE:蛋黄酱
你往三明治上放的东西
You put it on a sandwich.
萨拉米香肠  凤尾鱼  果酱
Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
白色的
It's white.
纸  雪  鬼
Paper. Snow. A ghost!
它使用鸡蛋做的
It's made from eggs.
小鸡
Chickens?
过
Pass.
KETCHUP:调味蕃茄酱
你往汉堡包上放的东西
You put this on a hamburger.
番茄酱  辣酱
Ketchup! Relish!
SODA: 苏打水
停
Stop!
哦  时间到
Oh, time's up. Well,
乔伊  你…
Joey, you were...
差点儿就上榜了  金...
...almost on a roll there. Gene...
你下半场还可能有机会进入决胜圈的
...you'll have a chance to go to the Winner's Circle,
但是现在
but now...
亨瑞达
...Henrietta,
你待会儿将进入决胜圈一试运气赢取一万美金
you're going to the Winner's Circle to try your luck for $ 10,000...
广告时间  不要走开
...right after this. Don't go away.
停
And we're out.
我们没赢又怎样呢
Oh, so we didn't win.
乐在其中也不错  对吧
But it's fun to play the game, right?
我有个孩子刚上大学
I got a kid starting college.
我的膝盖要做手术
I have to get surgery on my knee.
你刚刚让我损失一万美金
You just lost me 10 grand.
喔
Oh, wow.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我保证下一轮我们发挥好一点
Okay, I promise, we'll do better next time.
我会发挥好一些
Well, I will,
因为我不会跟你搭档了
because I won't be playing with you.
你要知道  有些题目也太难了点
Hey, some of those are pretty hard.
例如我的冰箱里怎么会有鬼的
Like, why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
是啊
Yeah.
-那么  星期六晚上   -我很愿意
- So Saturday night? - I'd love to.
太好了
Great.
你怎么这么长时间才约我
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
呃  这听起来有些愚蠢  但是...
Oh, well, this is gonna sound kind of silly...
你还记得我的室友 钱德勒·宾
...but do you remember my roommate, Chandler Bing?
当然  他在你的"乐队"里
Sure. He was in your "band."
已经16年了
It's been 16 years,
不过那个引号还是挺伤人的
but the air quotes still hurt.
对不起
Sorry.
没关系
That's okay. Anyway....
总之  我们那时都很喜欢你
Well, he and I both really liked you a lot...
但是我们又不想
...but we didn't want it
为此伤友谊
to jeopardize our friendship,
所以我们约定
so we made a pact...
谁也不能跟你约会
...that neither of us could ask you out.
-真的   -是啊  怎么了
- Really? - Yeah, why?
呃  我和钱德勒曾经亲热啊
Well, Chandler and I used to make out.
而且经常
A lot.
-是吗   -对呀
- You did? - Yeah.
我们常在下课后到实验室去
We'd go to the science lab after-hours.
还在我的地盘上
And on my turf?!
嘿  那家伙还没来
Hey, where is this guy?
都一个多小时了
It's been over an hour.
他要从新泽西赶过来
He's coming from Jersey.
他说会尽快赶到的
He said he'd get here as fast as he could.
-谁呀   -警察
- Who is it? - It's the police.
是警察
The police!
没错  是"好身材"警官
That's right. It's Officer Goodbody.
出什么事啦  警官
What's the matter, officer?
是不是有人调皮了
Has someone been bad?
这么多楼梯
That's a lot of stairs.
老天
Boy.
你们应该告诉人家这栋楼没电梯
You should warn people there's no elevator.
我午饭不该吃墨西哥菜
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
你没事吧  警官…
Are you gonna be okay, Officer...?
"好身材"
Goodbody.
你非要那么说的话
If you say so.
那么  哪位是
So where's the young lady...
我要"逮捕"的年轻女士啊
...who I am supposed to take downtown?
我的天啊
Oh, God.
谁告诉我在哪接我的录音机
Somebody show me where to plug in my box...
我们开始狂欢吧
...and we'll get this party started.
-在这   -对啊
- Over here? - Yeah.
-好吧  -瑞秋
- All right. - Rachel?
-啊   -呃  你是不是在开我的玩笑
- Yeah? - Are you kidding?
好吧  我们原来不知道你想要脱衣舞男
We didn't know you wanted a stripper,
所以我们借助于电话簿
so we went to the phone book...
找到第一个名字就打了过去
...and got the first name we could find.
你们的电话簿有多老了
How old's your phone book?
我的天啊
Oh, my God,
这个男人要在我的公寓里脱光光
this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
上帝  不要
God, no.
我可不想看他跳脱衣舞
I don't wanna see him take his clothes off.
你是在说我吗
Are you talking about me?
不
No.
我是说  我们显然是要看你跳脱衣舞的
I mean, obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
你这个养眼的万人迷
You big piece of eye candy.
好的  女士们
Okay. Okay, ladies,
请注意了
can I have your attention, please?
哦  好
Oh, yeah.
有人呼唤法律的巨擘了吗
Did someone call for the long arm of the law?
我要警告你
I should warn you,
我有秘密武器呦
I have a concealed weapon.
我希望你们熟悉本州的刑法
I hope you're familiar with this state's penal code.
好了好了  玩笑开够了
Okay, okay. Enough teasing.
现在该乐一乐了
Now for some pleasing.
她躲我
She cringed.
我兴奋的时候  就是这样的
This is how I look when I'm turned-on.
你们刚才就是在说我
You were talking about me before.
我可不需要这些
Look, I don't need this.
我要走了  我的帽子呢
I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
我干这行已经很长时间了
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
骇人听闻
Shocking.
现在  你付我300块
Now, if you'll just pay me my $300,
我这就走人
I'll be on my way.
300块  你开什么玩笑
$300? Are you kidding?
没关系  我来拿支票
That's okay. Let me get my checkbook.
不  你不用付他钱
No. You're not gonna pay him.
他什么也没干
He didn't do anything.
什么也没干
Didn't do anything?
我大老远的从毫尔伯肯搭公交车赶来
I took a bus all the way from Hoboken.
我爬了  天知道的  上亿的台阶
I climbed, I don't know, like, a billion stairs.
这两样儿
And it's not like
我可不是能一次完成的
I can take them two at a time.
我不管
I don't care.
我们才不会就为这个付给你300块钱
We're not paying you $300 for this.
那好  你那么保守
It's not my fault
欣赏不了男性的身材和魅力
if you're too uptight to appreciate...
这又不是我的错
...the male form in all its glory.
哦  是  我保守
Okay, I'm uptight.
所以我不想看个半大老头儿
That's why I don't wanna watch a middle-aged guy...
穿一身我只能认为是
...dance around in what I can only assume
小孩万圣节的行头跳脱衣舞
is a child's Halloween costume.
我也许是从我侄子那儿借的衣服
I may have borrowed this from my nephew...
但我担保衣服里头
...but let me assure you,
可是货真价实的真男人
what's underneath is all man.
抱歉
I'm sorry,
你是说真男人还是老男人
did you say "all man" or "old man"?
你可真刻薄
You're mean.
-瞧  警官…  -该死
- Look, officer-- Sir? - Damn it.
没想到吧
Big surprise.
大块头也会感情丰富
The hunk of beef has feelings.
鼓掌
Applause.
好  亨瑞达
Okay, Henrietta,
你选了"男人女人去山顶"（儿歌）
you picked "Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill."
我朋友瑞秋有个小孩
My friend Rachel has a kid.
我对儿歌很熟悉
I totally know nursery rhymes.
乔伊  描述以下
Joey, describe these things associated
跟美国国会有关的事物
with the United States Congress.
限时20秒
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
预备  开始
Ready? Go.
LEGISLATURE:立法机构
过
Pass.
ROTUNDA:圆形大厅
过
Pass.
FILIBUSTER:在立法机构中采用阻碍策略
过
Pass.
ADDENDUM:附录
-你喉咙后面挂着的小东西   -悬雍垂
- The thing hanging in your throat. - Uvula.
那过
Then pass.
JOINT SESSION:上下两议院的联席会议
好了  亨瑞达
Okay. Henrietta,
你没有得到所需的分数
you didn't get all the points you needed...
所以  那就意味着
...so that means,
金  你将进入决胜圈来赢取一万美金
Gene, you are going to the Winner's Circle to try for $ 10,000.
而且你将与乔伊·崔比安尼一起搭档
And you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
你跟米西·戈尔伯格亲热过
You made out with Missy Goldberg?
你怎么能在向我保证过之后还这么做
How could you do that after you promised me?
失陪一下
Excuse me.
你那么说  让我们听起来一点不像同性恋
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
你违反了君子协定
You broke the pact.
罗斯  那是16年前的事了
Ross, that was 16 years ago.
那也不行
That doesn't matter.
现在说的是我们之间友谊的基础
We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
我以为我们之间友谊的基础是难堪的发型
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
好吧  你看
All right, look.
要是我们真的明算账的话
If we're really gonna do this,
你也不是没干过违反君子协定的事
it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
-我没有   -真的
- I didn't. - Oh, really?
-没有   -真的
- No. - Oh, really?
-没有   -艾德丽安·特娜
- No. - Adrienne Turner.
在
Yes?
-嘿  艾德丽安  -嘿  艾德丽安  嘿
- Hey, Adrienne. - Hey, Adrienne. Hey.
我从没跟艾德丽安·特娜搅和到一起
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
哦  得了吧
Oh, please.
你知道我有多喜欢他
And you knew how much I liked her.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
A真的  还记得大一那年圣诞节假期前一个星期
Really? Remember that party freshman year?
那个大狂欢吗  我记得
A week before Christmas vacation? I do.
当时有人来找你
You had some visitors.
难以置信我们在一个真的大学聚会上
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
我兴奋得直想尿尿
I have to pee so bad.
这可真棒
This is so awesome.
大学男生好可爱
College guys are so cute.
嘿  你有男朋友了
Hey, you've got a boyfriend.
我知道
I know.
不过要是有个象克瑞·哈姆那样的想亲我
But if a guy who looks like Corey Haim wants to kiss me,
我是不会拒绝的
I am so gonna let him.
看  那是钱德勒
Hey, look, there's Chandler.
罗斯的白痴朋友
That stupid friend of Ross'
说我胖的那个
who said I was fat.
你要知道  我都瘦掉4磅了
You know, I've already lost four pounds.
就是  一眼就看得出来
You can so totally tell.
我就知道
I know!
过去看看
Well, let's see,
他可能知道罗斯在哪
maybe he knows where Ross is.
嘿  怎么样
Hey, how's it going?
-你不是...  -对  瑞秋
- Aren't you...? - Yeah, Rachel.
这是罗斯的妹妹  莫妮卡
And this is Ross' sister, Monica.
我们感恩节见过
We met at Thanksgiving.
对  最近如何
Right. So how you doing?
再好不过
Bitchen.
-嗨  莫妮卡   -嗨  钱德勒
- Hi, Monica. - Hi, Chandler.
见到你很高兴...才怪
It's really nice to see you. Not!
好吧
Okay.
我看看能不能找到罗斯
I'll see if I can find Ross.
哦我的天  瑞秋  充气椅
Oh, my God, Rach. Beanbag chairs.
千万别让我坐上去
Do not let me sit in one of those.
不然我坐那几天也不会起来
We'll be here for days.
听着  艾德丽安
Listen, Adrienne,
你可不能告诉钱德勒这件事
you can't tell Chandler about this.
哦  相信我  罗斯
Oh, believe me, Ross,
我不会告诉任何人的
I won't be telling anybody about this.
酷
Cool.
我以为你不知道
I didn't know you knew about that.
但是我知道了  我还很伤心
Well, I did. And it hurt.
所以我才写了《在休息室被背叛》那首歌
That's when I wrote the song "Betrayal in the Common Room."
嘿  对不起
Man, I'm sorry.
好了  那都是陈年往事了
Look, that was a long time ago.
那  我跟艾德丽安亲热
So I made out with Adrienne,
而你跟米西亲热
and you made out with Missy.
我看我们俩扯平了
Well, I guess we're even.
我们俩扯平了  对吧
We are even, right?
还有一件事
One more thing.
那晚我特生你的气
I was so pissed at you that night,
想报复你
I wanted to get back at you.
所以我当时想
So I thought,
"谁是罗斯最喜欢的人呢"
"Who does Ross like more than anybody?"
你对我妈做了什么
What did you do to my mom?
不是她
Not her.
我可真醉了
I am so drunk.
那就怪了
That's weird.
我跟你喝的差不多
I've had the same number of beers as you
怎么我一点没感觉
and don't feel anything.
你俩玩儿得愉快吗
So you girls having fun?
跟你说  好的不得了
For your information, ass-munch...
我瘦了4磅
...I've lost four pounds.
没准儿跳完舞会瘦到5磅
Maybe even five with all the dancing.
-有人定比萨饼了吗   -哦  是我
- Somebody order a pizza? - Oh, that's me!
我明天的入学考试算是没戏了
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
那  明年也许你可以到我们这儿来上大学
Well, maybe you could go to school here next year
我们可以一块玩玩
and we could totally hang out.
哦  对  好主意
Oh, yeah. There's a plan.
那我干脆现在就吃点脑灵通得了
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
没准儿你能拿到选美奖学金呢
Well, maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
别骗人了
What a line.
-那  你都申请了哪些学校   -唔..
- So where are you applying to? - Well...
你知道  我觉着我要去的地方应该阳光明媚
You know,l think it's kind of really important
这很重要  所以我想…
that I go somewhere where there's sun.
所以我想...嗨
So I'm sort of-- Hey!
我是大学生  还是乐队成员
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
那好吧
Yeah, okay.
怎么啦
What's the matter?
你们没见过
You never saw
五十岁的脱衣舞男哭吗
a 50-year-old stripper cry before?
好吧
You know, it's fine.
我们付你钱还不行吗
We'll pay you.
不不  你说得对
No, no, you're right.
我在开谁的玩笑
Who am I kidding?
早几年我就该挂起那逃脱三角绷带  不干了
I should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago.
现在我该怎么办
What am I gonna do? I mean...
我是说  我干这个都32年了
...this has been my life for 32 years.
我只会在人家面前脱衣服
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
不  等等  一定还有别的事你能做的
No, wait, there's got to be something else that you can do.
我是说  你还有什么技术吗
I mean, what skills do you have?
我不知道
I don't know.
我能让我的胸肌跳舞
I can make my pecs dance.
我可以用屁股蛋儿夹起1美元
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
而在我的内心深处
I can go to that special place inside me
并无羞愧之意
where I feel no shame.
那你也许可以从政
So maybe something in an office.
或者你可以教人跳脱衣舞
Or you could-- You could teach stripping.
你知道吗  分享你的天赋  发扬光大
You know, share your gift. Pass the torch.
对呀  这主意不赖
You know, actually, that's not a bad idea.
我可以在我的公寓外头教
I could do it out of my apartment.
我想我妈不会介意的
I don't think my mom would mind.
这下好啦
There you go.
你感觉好一点了吧
Okay. You think you're gonna be okay?
-对  好点了 -好
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
太奇怪了
This is so weird.
你永远不会知道什么时候
You never know when it's gonna be
是你的最后一舞
your last dance.
而且我甚至都没能跳完最后一支舞
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
那你把它跳完吧
Finish it.
-什么   -你的最后一次  给我们跳完吧
- What? - Your last dance. Do it for us.
-你当真   -你当真
- Really? - Really?
是的  他应该最后再做
Yeah. Yeah, he deserves to do
一次他喜爱的事
the thing he loves one last time.
好的  准备好了  女士们
Okay. All right. Get ready, ladies.
好了
Okay.
这可真让人兴奋
Oh, this is so hot!
别  别停下来
Oh, no, don't stop.
跳不动了
Have to.
欢迎来到决胜圈
Welcome to the Winner's Circle.
乔伊  金  你们准备好了吗
Joey, Gene, you guys ready?
-好了   -当然
- Yeah. - Sure.
好  限时60秒
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
预备  开始
Ready? Go.
TYPES OF TREES:树种
橡树  枫树  榆树  桦树
Oak. Maple. Elm. Birch.
我...我不知道  树种
I don't know. Types of trees...?
SPANISH WORDS:西班牙单词
早安  玉米卷饼  请
Buenos dias. Enchilada. Por favor.
哦  抱歉  西班牙单词我一个不认识
Oh, I'm so sorry, I don't know any Spanish words.
THINGS THAT BURN:可燃烧之物  有灼痛感之物
火柴  蜡烛
A match. A candle.
扑灭时发出"嗞"声的东西
Things that go: when you put them out.
火炬  篝火
A torch. A bonfire.
-哦  你的小便   -燃烧物
- Your pee. - Things that burn.
WHAT A DOG MIGHT SAY:狗狗会说什么
我要去散散步
"I'd like to go for a walk."
挠挠我的肚皮
"Scratch my belly."
哥们儿  我觉得你说的太乱了
Dude. Dude, I think you're losing it.
我有毛  我会吠叫
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
哦  这狗说的好啊
What a dog says.
PIZZA TOPPINGS:比萨饼料
-意大利辣香肠  -比萨饼料  下一个
- Pepperoni. - Pizza toppings!Next.
SUPERMODELS:超级模特
辛迪·克劳馥  克莉斯蒂·布林克利
Cindy Crawford. Christie Brinkley.
海蒂·克劳姆  克劳迪娅·西佛
Heidi Klum. Claudia Schiffer.
克莉斯蒂·特林顿  凯特·玛斯
Christy Turlington. Kate Moss.
钱德勒永远追不上的女孩
Girls Chandler could never get?
-超级名模   -哪儿
- Supermodels. - Where?
嘿  瑞秋在哪
Hey. Where's Rachel?
她和菲比送脱衣舞男上医院了
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
你知不知道钱德吻过瑞秋
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
什么  什么时候
What? When was this?
1987年
1987.
你们俩上学校找我去的那个周末
The weekend you guys visited me at school.
我的天  那也太疯狂了
Oh, my God. That's wild.
是  不过那是很久以前的事了
But it was, like, a million years ago.
-没什么要紧的   -但那对我很要紧
- It doesn't matter. - It matters to me.
为什么
Why?
因为你吻瑞秋的那晚
Because the night you kissed Rachel...
也是我第一次吻瑞秋
...was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
你那晚也吻瑞秋了
You kissed her that night too?
一晚上两个男人
Two guys in one night?
我还以为她整过鼻子以后
Oh, I thought she became a slut
才变得放荡了呢
after she got her nose fixed.
说真的  你在哪儿吻的瑞秋
Seriously, where did this happen?
是这样的
Okay...
你告诉我瑞秋在我们屋里睡了之后
...after you told me she was passed out in our room...
我进去看看她怎么样了
...l went in there to make sure she was all right.
她躺在我床上
She was lying on my bed,
睡在一堆衣服下面
all buried in people's coats.
我过去想吻她的额头
I went to kiss her on the forehead...
但屋里太暗
...but it was so dark,
我不小心亲到了她的嘴唇
I accidentally got her lips.
我想离开
I started to pull away,
但我觉得她也开始吻我
but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
那只有一瞬间但感觉太奇妙了
It was only for a second, but it was amazing.
但是现在  我却发现你先吻了她
And now I find out that you kissed her first.
等等  你刚才说她在哪张床上
Wait, what bed did you say she was on?
我床上
Mine.
我记得很清楚我把她放到我床上的
I'm sure I put her on my bed.
不对  她肯定是在我床上
No, she was definitely on my bed.
我干吗吻完一个女孩后把她放到你床上
Why would I kiss a girl and then put her on your bed?
那当时我床上的是谁
Well, then who was on my bed?
哦  哦  哦
Oh, oh, oh...
不  不  不
No! No! No!
是的
Yes!
你在那堆衣服下面
You were under the pile of coats?
那堆衣服就是我
I was the pile of coats!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
你是我的午夜神秘接吻人
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
你是我和瑞秋的初吻
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
你就是我这辈子的初吻
You were my first kiss ever?!
瞧瞧我结的什么亲家
What did I marry into?!
完蛋了
Crap!